Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - Army of Northern Virginia, General Orders, Cavalry Division no.9, 1863; 228268 (Box 4, Folder C664)
  - Special Orders no.6 (photocopy), 1865; 228267 (Box 4, Folder C665)
  - C.S.A. Army Dept. of Northern Virginia Resolutions of the Texas Brigade, 1865; 228266 (Box 4, Folder C669)
  - General Orders Headquarters Wheelers Cavalry Corps (photocopy) no.4, 1864; 228265 (Box 4, Folder C676)
  - C.S.A. Army Dept. of Tennessee. Memorial [concerning the retention and procurement of troops] to the Congress of the Confederate States, 1863; 228264 (Box 4, Folder C678)
  - Soldiers! You are again about to encounter... (photocopy), 1861; 228263 (Box 4, Folder C691)
  - A proclamation to the good people of the counties of Alexandria... Broadside (photocopy), 1861; 228262 (Box 4, Folder C696)
  - C.S.A. Army Dept. of the Valley. Forsberg's Brigade. Resolutions of Forsberg's Brigade, Wharton's Division, 1865; 228261 (Box 4, Folder C697)
  - To the people of Western Virginia, Broadside, September 14, 1862; 228260 (Box 4, Folder C749)
  - Special Order [Tahlequah] (photocopy), 1862; 228259 (Box 4, Folder C766)
  - Headquarters, Dist. of Texas, General orders no.4, January 30, 1865; 228258 (Box 4, Folder C774)
  - To the militia of the parishes... (photocopy), 1862?; 228257 (Box 4, Folder C791)
  - General Orders. Headquarters Trans-Miss. Dept. [Shreveport, 1864] no.91 broadside, 228256 (Box 4, Folder C798)
  - General Orders no.44 (photocopy)(lacking no.38), May 19, 1862; 228255 (Box 4, Folder C808)
  - C.S.A. Bureau of Public Printing. Report of the Superintendent of Public Printing, 1864; 228254 (Box 4, Folder C816)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Report of the Attorney General..., February 26, 1862; 228253 (Box 4, Folder C824)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Communication, March 13, 1863; 228252 (Box 4, Folder C826)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Communication from Attorney General, December 15, 1863; 228251 (Box 4, Folder C827)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice Communication from Attorney General, January 9, 1864; 228250 (Box 4, Folder C828)
  - C.S.A. Dept of Justice. Report of the Attorney General, January 1, 1863; 228249 (Box 4, Folder C833)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Report of the Attorney General, November 18, 1863; 228248 (Box 4, Folder C834)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Report of the Attorney General, April 25, 1864; 228247 (Box 4, Folder C835)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of Justice. Report of the Attorney General, 1864; 228246 (Box 4, Folder C836)
  - C.S.A. Dept of Justice. Report of Vessels sunk and burnt in the Pamukey River, by Captain Chas. S. Carrington, A.Q.M., under the orders of General Joseph E. Johnston and others, 1863; 228245 (Box 4, Folder C837)
  - C.S.A. Dept. of State. Communication from the Secretary of State [in answer to the inquiry whether any state of the United States has, directly or indirectly, intimated a desire or willingness to make overtures of peace], November 18, 1864; 228244 (Box 4, Folder C838)
  - Correspondence of the Department of State, in relation to the British Consul's residence, 1863; 228243 (Box 4, Folder C839)
  - C.S.A. District Courts. Virginia. Decisions of Hon. James D. Halyburton, Judge of the C.S. District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia in the cases of John B. Lane and John H. Leftwich, in relation to their exemption as mail contractors from the performance of military service, 1864; 228242 (Box 4, Folder C848)
  - C.S.A. District Courts. South Carolina. Sequestration Cases, 1861; 228241 (Box 4, Folder C850)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Communication from Secretary of the Navy, March 9, 1863; 228240 (Box 4, Folder C861)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Communication from the Secretary of the Navy, December 21, 1864; 228239 (Box 4, Folder C862)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Communication from the Secretary of the Navy, January 4, 1865; 228238 (Box 4, Folder C863)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Communication of Secretary of the Navy, January 31, 1864; 228237 (Box 4, Folder C864)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Communication from Secretary of the Navy, February 15, 1865; 228236 (Box 4, Folder C865)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Letter of Secretary of Navy, April 7, 1862; 228235 (Box 4, Folder C874)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Letter of Secretary of the Navy (Navy Register), September 8, 1862; 228234 (Box 4, Folder C877)
  - Register of the Commissioned and Warrant Officers of the Navy of the C.S.A. 14p., 1863; 228233 (Box 4, Folder C881)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Register, 1864; 228232 (Box 4, Folder C882)
  - C.S.A. Navy Dept. Report of the Secretary of the Navy. 96p. (pp.53-96 missing), January 1, 1864; 228231 (Box 4, Folder C888)
  - C.S.A. Patent Office. Annual Report of the Commissioner of Patents, January 26, 1865; 228230 (Box 4, Folder C896)
  - C.S.A. Patent Office. Report of the Commissioner of Patents, January 1862; 228229 (Box 4, Folder C897)
  - C.S.A. Patent Office Report, 1863; 228228 (Box 4, Folder C898)
  - Report of the Commissioner of Patents, 1864; 228227 (Box 4, Folder C899)
  - C.S.A. Post-Office Dept. Report of the Postmaster General to the President, April 29, 1861; 228226 (Box 4, Folder C917)
  - C.S.A. Post Office Dept. Communication from the Postmaster General, September 29, 1862; 228225 (Box 4, Folder C920)
  - C.S.A. Post Office Dept. Report... telegraph companies, October 13, 1862; 228224 (Box 4, Folder C922)
  - C.S.A. Post Office Dept. Report of the Postmaster General, December 7, 1863; 228223 (Box 4, Folder C923)
  - C.S.A. Post Office Dept. Report of the Postmaster General, May 2, 1864; 228222 (Box 4, Folder C924)
  - C.S.A. Post Office Dept. Report of the Postmaster General, November 7, 1864; 228221 (Box 4, Folder C925)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Medical Director's Office. Circular (Broadside) 1p., November 26, 1862; 228220 (Box 4, Folder C935)
  - Duties of the Chief Matron (photocopy), 186-; 228219 (Box 4, Folder C1034)
  - Duties of the Ward Master (photocopy), 186-; 228218 (Box 4, Folder C1035)
  - Hospital Regulations, July 1, 1863; 228217 (Box 4, Folder C1044)
  - A Manual of Military Surgery, 1863; 228216 (Box 4, Folder C1057)
  - A Manual of Military Surgery (extensive fire damage-Saved from the Great Fire of Richmond, Va. 1865), 1863; 228215 (Box 4, Folder C1057c.2)
  - Regulations for the Medical Department of the Confederate States Army, 1861; 228214 (Box 5, Folder C1060)
  - Regulations for the Medical Department of the C.S. Army, 1862; 228213 (Box 5, Folder C1061)
  - C.S.A. Surgeon-General's Office. Standard Supply Table of the Indigenous Remedies for Field Service and the Sick in General Hospitals, 1863; 228212 (Box 5, Folder C1065)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Abstract of Drafts of Members of the C.S. House of Representatives, paid by E.D. Elmore, Treasurer C.S., during the recess of Congress, after April 18th, 1863, under authority of Act of April 16th, 1862, 228211 (Box 5, Folder C1066)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Additional Estimates for the Support of the Government, February 11. 1864; 228210 (Box 5, Folder C1067)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Circular [about] an error having occurred in regulations of March 25, 1863 for carrying into effect "An Act to Provide for the Funding and Further Issue of Treasury Notes", June 27, 1863; 228209 (Box 5, Folder C1080)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication accompanying copies of circulars issued in respect to the produce loan, 1862; 228208 (Box 5, Folder C1083)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report claims of deceased soldiers, 1863; 228207 (Box 5, Folder C1090)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury, May 10, 1864; 228206 (Box 5, Folder C1096)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury in reference to the amount of funds paid into the Treasury under the operation of the sequestration act, February 25, 1863; 228205 (Box 5, Folder C1091)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication recommending certain changes in the impressment laws, 1864; 228204 (Box 5, Folder C1098)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication recommending certain changes in the impressment laws, 1864; 228203 (Box 5, Folder C1099)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of the Treasury submitting estimate of appropriation for the purchase of cotton, for the purpose of procuring the means of paying, in coin, the interest on certificate of indebtedness, May 25, 1864; 228202 (Box 5, Folder C1100)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury concerning change of old issue of treasury notes for new, November 23, 1864; 228201 (Box 5, Folder C1101)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury covering estimate for additional appropriation required by the Navy Department, November 28, 1864; 228200 (Box 5, Folder C1103)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury submitting the report of second auditor relative to amount of claims from each of the states paid, or allowed under the act of June 14, 1864, December 7, 1864; 228199 (Box 5, Folder C1104)
  - Message of the President, January 5, 1865; 228198 (Box 5, Folder C1107)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury relative to unpaid requisitions upon the Treasury drawn by the quartermaster general and the commissary general, January 5, 1865; 228197 (Box 5, Folder C1109)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury concerning an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Navy Department, January 28, 1865; 228196 (Box 5, Folder C1110)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury, February 1, 1865; 228195 (Box 5, Folder C1111)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury transmitting an estimate for an additional appropriation required to meet the expenses of the Department of Justice during the six months ending June 30, 1865, February 1, 1865; 228194 (Box 5, Folder C1112)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury transmitting estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Navy Department, February 8, 1865; 228193 (Box 5, Folder C1113)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury covering an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Department of Justice, February 11, 1865; 228192 (Box 5, Folder C1114)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of Treasury, Februray [sic] 20, 1865; 228191 (Box 5, Folder C1115)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication from Secretary of Treasury submitting papers in relation to certain instructions issued from this department, to carry into execution the tax laws, February 20, 1865; 228190 (Box 5, Folder C1116)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communication of Secretary of the Treasury, February 28th, 1865; 228189 (Box 5, Folder C1117)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communications from the Secretary relative to tax in kind for year 1863 18p., 1864; 228188 (Box 5, Folder C1121)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communications from the Secretary and the attorney general in regard to the sequestration of real estate belonging to alien enemies, 1863; 228187 (Box 5, Folder C1122)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Communications of Secretary submitting estimates of additional appropriations required for the support of the government, May 2, 1864; 228186 (Box 5, Folder C1123)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Documents... Report of the Commissioner of taxes, 1863; 228185 (Box 5, Folder C1125)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimate of an additional appropriation required..., 1862; 228184 (Box 5, Folder C1126)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimate of an additional appropriation required for the service of gout..., February 18-April 1, 1862; 228183 (Box 5, Folder C1128)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimate of an additional appropriation required for the service of the Post Office dept., 1862; 228182 (Box 5, Folder C1129)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimate of an Appropriation required for the redemption of such treasury notes... rendered unfit for circulation, 1862; 228181 (Box 5, Folder C1130)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimates of additional appropriations required for the service of the Navy Dept., February 18, 1862; 228180 (Box 5, Folder C1132)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimates of an Appropriation for the purchase of coin, 1862; 228179 (Box 5, Folder C1133)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Estimates of Appropriations for the support of the govt. up to the 28th of Feb. 1862, from Feb 28. to Apr. 1, 1862, 228178 (Box 5, Folder C1134)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. The following regulations and instructions for carrying into effect the act of February 17, 1864, 228177 (Box 5, Folder C1137)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Instructions for Collectors of Taxes, 1863; 228176 (Box 5, Folder C1140)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Instructions for the agents for collecting subscriptions to the produce loan, 1862; 228175 (Box 5, Folder C1141)
  - C.S.A. House Committee of Ways and Means. Letter about tax-in-kind, November 21, 1864; 228174 (Box 5, Folder C1145)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter to the Commissioners appointed to receive subscriptions to the produce loan..., October 15, 1861; 228173 (Box 5, Folder C1147)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter of the Secretary submitting the report of the auditor, 1862; 228172 (Box 5, Folder C1149)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter of the Secretary enclosing an estimate of the amount required for the telegraphic service, to June 30th, 1863, January 12, 1863; 228171 (Box 5, Folder C1150)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter of the Secretary covering estimates of sums needed for the public service among the Indian tribes, December 10, 1863; 228170 (Box 5, Folder C1151)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter of Secretary showing the additional amount necessary to meet the estimated expenses of the Department of Justice, for the half year ending June 30, 1865, December 10, 1864; 228169 (Box 5, Folder C1152)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Letter of Secretary transmitting statement sowing certain transfers of appropriations required for the service of the Treasury Dept., December 12, 1864; 228168 (Box 5, Folder C1153)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Open letter to the banks concerning the act of Congress to reduce the currency, 1864; 228167 (Box 5, Folder C1157)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Regulations as to bonds and certificates of stock..., 1862; 228166 (Box 5, Folder C1160)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Regulations established for the disposal at private sale of the six percent non-taxable bonds of the C.S., 1864; 228165 (Box 5, Folder C1163)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Regulations established in relation to the receipt of four percent bonds and certificates offered in payment for taxes, 1864; 228164 (Box 5, Folder C1165)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Regulations in relation to the issue of certificates for bonds and registered stock, February 25, 1863; 228163 (Box 5, Folder C1168)
  - C.S.A. Treasury dept. Regulations prescribed for the act to prohibit the importation of luxuries, February 6, 1864; 228162 (Box 5, Folder C1172)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Regulations to authorize the depositaries of the Treasury to receive balances in the hands of postmasters in the C.S., March 12, 1864; 228161 (Box 5, Folder C1174)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report of the Secretary to Congress submitting information from the various state governments in regard to the value of the property, the revenue system, and the amount collected during the last fiscal year in each of the Confederate States, 1861; 228160 (Box 5, Folder C1178)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report of the Secretary, May 2, 1864; 228159 (Box 5, Folder C1184)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report of Secretary, May 2, 1864; 228158 (Box 5, Folder C1185)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report of the Secretary, November 7, 1864; 228157 (Box 5, Folder C1186)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Report on the condition of government cotton, contiguous to the Mississippi and its tributaries, May 16, 1864; 228156 (Box 5, Folder C1187)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Response of the Secretary to the resolution of the Senate of the 5th December 1864, respecting operations under the act to impose regulations upon the foreign commerce of the C.S., December 12, 1864; 228155 (Box 5, Folder C1188)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Revenue depots referred to at page 4 Broadside, n.d.; 228154 (Box 5, Folder C1189)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Special report of the Secretary of the Treasury on the subject of the finances, January 9, 1865; 228153 (Box 5, Folder C1197)
  - C.S.A Treasury Dept. Tabular statement showing the rates of duty upon merchandise under the tariff act of 1857, of the United States, as amended by the Provisional Congress of the Confederate States of America, 1861; 228152 (Box 5, Folder C1203)
  - C.S.A. Treasury Dept. Treasury Circular no.1-14, XXX; 228151 (Box 5, Folder C1205)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Army regulations, adopted for the use of the Army of the C.S., 1861; 228150 (Box 5, Folder C1207)
  - Army Regulations adopted for the use of the Army of the Confederate States, 1861; 228149 (Box 5, Folder C1211)
  - Circular... Richmond Broadside (photocopy), 1864; 228148 (Box 5, Folder C1241)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Circular [from] C.S. Central Laboratory, April 30, 1864; 228147 (Box 5, Folder C1254)
  - C.S.A. Communication... drunkenness, 1862; 228146 (Box 5, Folder C1261)
  - C.S.A. War dept. Communication of the Secretary of War enclosing an estimate of funds required by the Ordnance Bureau, January 27, 1863; 228145 (Box 5, Folder C1264)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary of War covering reports from Surgeon General and the Chief of Engineers, February 3, 1863; 228144 (Box 5, Folder C1268)
  - C.S.A. War dept. Communication from the Secretary covering an estimate of the amount required for the remuneration of additional clerks in the War Dept., February 5, 1863; 228143 (Box 5, Folder C1271)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary transmitting the report of General John H. Winder, listing the civilians in custody under authority of the War Department, in the city of Richmond, February 14, 1863; 228142 (Box 5, Folder C1274)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary enclosing a report from the quartermaster general, with regard to the number of quartermasters on duty in Richmond, February 17, 1863; 228141 (Box 5, Folder C1275)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary of War enclosing a list of the civilian prisoners in custody at Salisbury, North Carolina, under military authority, February 27, 1863; 228140 (Box 5, Folder C1278)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary transmitting estimate of additional funds required for the service of the Ordnance Bureau, for the period ending 30th June 1863, March 3, 1863; 228139 (Box 5, Folder C1279)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary of War transmitting claims for vessels seized for the public use, March 11, 1863; 228138 (Box 5, Folder C1280)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary of War relative to the exemption of mail contractors under the act of April 14, 1863, December 14, 1863; 228137 (Box 5, Folder C1284)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary covering a list of the officers of artillery in the provisional army, for the performance of ordnance duty, appointed since the 16th day of September, 1862 and the roll of merit reported by the Board of Examiners, December 19, 1863; 228136 (Box 5, Folder C1287)
  - Communication of the Secretary of War, January 11, 1864; 228135 (Box 5, Folder C1289)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary, January 15, 1864; 228134 (Box 5, Folder C1291)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary, January 23, 1864; 228133 (Box 5, Folder C1293)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary, January 27, 1864; 228132 (Box 5, Folder C1294)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of the Secretary covering an estimate of an additional sum needed by the Engineer Bureau, January 28, 1864; 228131 (Box 5, Folder C1295)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary, stating that the records of his office do not contain any authority to raise troops of conscript age, except in localities where the operation of the conscript law has been suspended, January 28, 1864; 228130 (Box 5, Folder C1296)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of the Secretary of War relative to the delivery of the "tax in kind" at the government depots by the producers, February 4, 1864; 228129 (Box 5, Folder C1300)
  - Communication of the Secretary of War, February 11, 1864; 228128 (Box 5, Folder C1301)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of the Secretary conveying information relative to general hospitals in and around Richmond, February 15, 1864; 228127 (Box 5, Folder C1303)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary covering a list of those who have been retired from the military service, in accordance with the provision of the act for ridding the army of ignorant, disabled, and incompetent officers, May 26, 1864; 228126 (Box 5, Folder C1304)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from the Secretary submitting an estimate for the steamer Phoenix, November 14, 1864; 228125 (Box 5, Folder C1305)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary relative to the act of June 14, 1864, November 17, 1864; 228124 (Box 5, Folder C1306)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary relative to the special exchange of prisoners of war by the Commissioner of Exchange, November 21, 1864; 228123 (Box 5, Folder C1307)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary relative to the recent impressment of clauses in the State of Virginia, November 28, 1864; 228122 (Box 5, Folder C1308)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary conveying information relative to the arrangements which have bee made "for the relief of our soldiers who are prisoners of war in the hands of the enemy", December 3, 1864; 228121 (Box 5, Folder C1309)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary relative to the appointments under an act approved June 14, 1864, December 3, 1864; 228120 (Box 5, Folder C1310)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary submitting an estimate of funds needed to meet a deficiency in the appropriation to pay the officers and employees of the department, December 6, 1864; 228119 (Box 5, Folder C1311)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary submitting an estimate of funds required to meet our treaty obligations to the Indian Nations for the period ending June 30th, 1865, December 7, 1864; 228118 (Box 5, Folder C1312)
  - Communication from the Secretary of War, December 15, 1864; 228117 (Box 5, Folder C1313)
  - Communication from the Secretary of War, December 20, 1864; 228116 (Box 5, Folder C1314)
  - Communication from the Secretary of War, December 21, 1864; 228115 (Box 5, Folder C1315)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary of War conveying information relative to the impressment of brandy, January 5, 1865; 228114 (Box 5, Folder C1317)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary conveying an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Bureau of Engineers, January 6, 1865; 228113 (Box 5, Folder C1318)
  - Communication of the Secretary of War, January 11, 1865; 228112 (Box 5, Folder C1319)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary covering a list of quartermasters and assistant quartermasters now in service, February 7, 1865; 228111 (Box 5, Folder C1321)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary conveying information relative to the number of iron furnaces and forges worked by agents of the governments or by contractors during the year 1864, February 14, 1865; 228110 (Box 5, Folder C1322)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary transmitting an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the department, February 15, 1865; 228109 (Box 5, Folder C1323)